係係係。
打。
係。
咁如果冇咧？
我哋按照翻個議程就係。
哦，O K，好好，O K。
就係誒，我可以宣佈。
噉啊，周浩鼎議員，你接唔接受？誒，接受嘅。
好，咁請問仲有冇其他委員嘅提名？
亦都需要由提名嘅委員接納，噉啊，請委員提名。
你按議程講嘅，你要唔要同主席講一講你嗰個？
之前有啲中文嘅組，係我見到係係復診，我考慮佢個服務都真係多得滯成為。
係，誒何君瑤議員提名周浩鼎議員，有冇人和議？噉我和議啦，嚇。
睇下先嚇，選舉主席與司庫舉行係啦係啦，就叫佢哋簡介呢兩個rules。好啊好啊，噉我而家可以叫佢哋入嚟。請請佢入。好啊好啊好啊。
嚇，周浩鼎議員係啊自動啊唔係係擔擔啊擔任本小組嘅委員會主席，噉啊請啊周浩鼎議員出嚟，好。
誒，根據在於內務守則第二十二條同埋附錄四嘅選舉程序，而家請委員提名一職一個人啦，係做人選嚇咁咧就誒有效嘅提名，需由一名委員口頭作出，並需由最少另外一位委員咧口頭附議嘅咁咧。
好。
嗯。
你想講嘅？
I don't know.
誒代表可以誒簡介一下個情況先，唔該。
噉我哋就請誒進入議程二咧，就我哋請香港律師會嘅代表可以誒進場嚇。
Thank you, Chairman. I'd like to speak in English because we have two team members English speaking. Yes.
And in one, I would like to highlight Rule 13.
The operation, we have come across some issues in the in the running of the scheme, and the amendments to the rules are aimed at enhancing the operation of the fund and providing more clarity to the PIS rules.
由法律顧問，就有關中國翻譯的議案，我們已向立法會秘書處回覆。
噉我現在咧就邀請香港律師會嘅代表向委員咧係簡介2016年誒律師專業離常修訂規則及2016年執業律誒律師執業修訂規則啊，擴誒括弧該兩項修訂規則，並闡述香港律。
律師會就小組委員會法律顧問於二零一六年十二月七日就關於二零一六年律師專業離常修訂規則嘅中文文本嘅事宜發出嘅函件，而於二零一六年十二月九日發出嘅復函畀立法會嘅內容。噉，我哋請律師會嘅誒。
We've submitted a legislative council brief, and in that brief we have introduced the amendments to the rules. The rules have been in operation for over thirty years, and during the course of
其實。
係啊。
We have.
explained in our letter.
五分鐘，五分鐘調運唔得。
除非主席有第第啲嘅睇法啊，OK，呢個首先聲明先。
That in fact, in our explain ah in our translation.
好誒，頭先剛才有委員好似舉咗手想問問題嘅，阿何君耀議員係。
We would like to. We'll be happy to answer any questions from members.
of the contribution, as well as to the claim and amount of the claim.
在其中，律師提出了關於翻譯的問題。
There should not be any ambiguity, because in the last sentence of Rule 13.
we can see that the translation has already highlighted that the provision relates to the dispute in relation to the liability and quantum.
所以爭議 relates to these two items, two aspects, and that we do not think that in the current translation, the Chinese version will raise any ambiguity, and we submit that this this version of the Chinese text be retained.
在立法會簡報，我們已經詳細解釋了我們修改相關條文的原因，我並不想重複。我只想回應問題。
主席。
誒。
嗯。
誒律師會嘅代表係。
It is suggested that.
所以， Chairman， is that。
and have done some recommendations.
in the in the current form of the amendments.
Queen's Council's suggestions are actually implemented.
The board has instructed a Queen's Counsel to conduct a review.
If I may, your question is directed at the Law Society's provision of the Queen's Counsel.
Report of the review and recommendations, so LECO could have a better idea of what the Queen's Council suggested.
No, I am referring to your brief to Lajcak, chairman, paragraph B bracket E, and in the paragraph.
我有啲追問嘅時候，我哋有第二輪嘅追問啦，好嘛？大家睇下委員可唔可以都同意噉樣，我哋就用噉嘅方式做好嘛？咁誒，第二位議員頭先舉咗手誒，想發問嘅。
So, I am wondering if the if the board is convenient to supply the review and recommendations to Letchko to us, so we could have a better idea of what the Queen's Counsel suggested.
誒主席，我純粹係先宣佈下少少嘅利益，因為我亦都係律師會嘅誒理事噉，但係誒喺度宣佈利益嘅，即係純粹係因為個工作嘅身份嘅問題。但我睇唔到有任何直接或間接嘅金錢上嘅利益，咁所以我喺呢一度先至聲明誒，亦都係參與嘅會議裏邊，我睇唔到有咩好大嘅問題。
我冇嘢問。好，誒，阿何議員問咗你嘅問題係咪？我提提議咗。O.K.，好誒，我諗我哋咧可以誒，或者我哋定個簡單嘅規矩咧，或者我哋每人問嘅問題連問連答五分鐘先啦，好嘛？咁如果稍後誒，我哋仲係未解決到有啲嘅問題，想要再。
未有係咪啊？啊啊！楊嶽橋議員係請。Yes, thank you, Chairman. Um, according to the呃law society's brief, the current amendments are suggested pursuant to a Queen's Council review, and I refer to paragraph B bracket E. And could the law society please provide the
gentleman.
and.
In an email.
Can you provide a timeline, or?
have been adopted to the current amendments.
所以，does it mean everything that the Queen's Council suggested?
When I get back to the office, okay. So this is an undertaking, I assume. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Thank you, chairman. Okay.
小段落 may impact other provisions in the rules. It was thought prudent to get a senior counsel to take a look at our suggestions.
Yes, the the original suggestions for the amendments actually came from the solicitors indemnity fund and/or or the council, but because
status of the fund and some breakdowns for types and amounts of claims, say in the past few three years, so we could have a better idea of the status of the fund, Chairman.
Scheme, but going back to 1989, so I'm sure that that the latest claims report is very easily shared. If that would be of interest, very well, gentlemen. So when are we going to have the relevant documents?
Sorry, is that? Yeah, thank you. Sorry, apologies. Please carry on. I said the the original suggestions for all the amendments to the rules, which impact on the operation of the schema, came either from the professional indemnity scheme, the company, or the council. But because the rules are fairly complex and changing a
Give us a tick if you like on the drafting and make sure that we'd achieve the objects that we wanted to. So the suggestions did not emanate from the QC. The QC was simply responding to the suggestions from the Solicitors Indemnity Fund and the Council. So, Chairman, I'm just simply asking: Is it convenient to have a look at the report or?
係。
好，跟住咧就請郭榮亨議員。
roundup the current reserves are approximately two billion Hong Kong dollars.
一減是是justify，所以yes，我mean，the precise amount of the reduction obviously is a matter of some some discussion。Okay，thank you。I look forward to having seeing further reduction on the premium for solicitors。Thank you。
To see if there are further room for reduction, because I understand the fund is actually doing quite well in terms of its finance, and there is a huge financial surplus right now. Can can you give us the figure and tell us whether there is further room for reduction for the premium? Thank you.
是代表從律師會建議，它不是必要，因為什麼？女王的顧問建議是非常微不足道，或一切已經完全採納了現行修正案。這是我的唯一擔憂。主席，所以會那會那種報告。
或，as you said that all the Queen's Council revealed opinion has already been incorporated in this draft amendment. That's correct. That's correct. So it has been fully adopted. Fully adopted. Okay. And my second part of my questions is it convenient for the Law Society or the Board to provide a report on the financial
Yes, please. Yes, certainly. I mean, the the fund has audited accounts. Sorry, the fund has audited accounts. And as managers, there is a a manager of the scheme, and we provide a quite comprehensive claims report every year. We have claim statistics on the professional indemnity
Thank you, Chairman. I have similar questions, but these questions perhaps do not relate directly to these amendments. But they are of significant interest by members of the profession, especially in relation to the financial status of the fund itself. Now, I understand there is always published reports.
about the financial status of the funds, but it is sometimes quite hard to understand the amount of discount that you put on the premium each year. Now, understand that in recent years you've given up to a fifty percent discount on the insurance premium payable by.
Members of the law society, which is encouraging, but I was just wondering whether there are room for further reduction in the future. The reason I ask is because for many of the practitioners, this is quite a heavy overhead, and that we are trying to reduce the burden on on them.
We are aware of the concern of members. If I may, I would suggest we don't use the word surplus, because you know we are a mutual scheme. So these are in fact reserves, and there is just a level of prudence which must be maintained against any future claims that might arise.
As such, I don't have anything further to add. Okay.
Thank you. Any other questions from other member?
We might need when you it's convenient to you provide some.
And Chairman，I I do think that I I can see from the question raised。
所以我 myself，我 open， if you do consider that there is really a lot
I personally have one question only， referring to the schedule three， there's a new paragraph eight。
Brief background, so that members follow each provisions much more easily and effectively. We hope that we do not need to hold too many meetings for this subsidiary legislation that the profession is also waiting.
and maybe legal adviser may have some points that if you want like to add because you may be most familiar or questions that can help speed up the whole process also。
amendment， you give us more statistics， and so we give a very good explanation and account to the to the public. This is what I request。法律顧問會唔會有嘢？Okay，下有冇有補充嗎？你有提出我哋。
as well as a sort of a joint responsibility that like everyone try to share a bit if in case some law firms go into problems. So I I want to raise this issue from a broader scope also as we have members who raise it.
That obviously protects not just the profession, but also the public. But as having said that, we are aware of the concern of members. The reduction in contribution was first made in 2010-11, and you're quite right that this last year the reduction went up to 50%. There is an
不可避免，緊張在於財政司長和議會之間，因為您們一定會明白，財政司長的職責是確保基金會妥善管理，所以他們必須考慮成員的利益，以及保護基金會。
I understand that, but there's a two billion dollar whatever you call it, the surplus reserved. Reserved. And what is the average claim against the fund on in the past few years? Our average claim figure is around 3.5 million dollars. Okay, so you've got more than
Enough to cover, you know, going forward. So there should be scope for further reduction of the premium payable by solicitors. Is that right? I think, as always, when faced with this decision, the board takes prudent actuarial advice. And in the past, the actuarial advice has been that.
Thank you。嗯，跟住下一位議員就係梁美芬議員。係主席。誒，其實呢個問題咧，而家我哋講緊即係誒附屬立法啦。呢個問題本身應該都傾過，以往都係傾過嘅。但係咧，亦都明白咧，今屆咧我哋係有新嘅議員。咁所以主席咧，我都覺得咧。
如果係啊，我哋嘅誒委員咧，佢對翻一啲基本嘅一啲誒資料需要咧，我哋係誒需要去提供，因為之後我哋係逐條去審議。誒，in in fact，I I hold the view that we we need to balance public interest with the interest of the profession. In fact
Of course, most members are practitioners here, either barrister or solicitors. We do consider, of course, the situation of our fellow members in the legal profession. But at the same time, from the point of Legislative Council, we do need to.
also make a good balance for protection of public interests, as you know, legal services receive high respect and confidence from the public, and if in case anything happen, those ordinary clients and victims should be reasonably protect.
already for reserve, we we can consider reduction. But really, we have to bear in mind the public's interest is there. As when we discuss, I remember in the previous terms talking about a professional indemnity. Actually, that is for the public.
因為。
and I, I, Mr. Ho,
所以那會係 rare，very rare，rare 情況，very rare，okay，yeah，okay。
And if there's a dispute at the moment, then that's only resolved by reference to the SC clause. But with this, we can actually take over conduct if if required. But I've never known it be used.
Yeah, Chair, maybe in this regards, perhaps it's not directly related to the existing proposed amendments that the law society seeking for. Anyway, if any member of this committee is interested about
save the defence costs. okay, and that would be regardless of the opinion of the, the law firm, the the indemnifier. yes, yes, yeah, and okay, okay. because the way the scheme works is that the the
the the defence of the claim is a joint retainer between the indemnified firm and and the company, right? We're joint clients instructing the defence solicitors, all right? So obviously we have to agree on all major steps in the litigation, but
Therefore, compensate the member of of the public if we think that you know you can see that an indemnified may not be able to satisfy any adverse costs order and so if in our view supported by an SC the matter really should be settled that gives us the option to step in and and and do that.
啊，maybe the representative from law society and also legal adviser, any? No, just to basically agree with that, and that's what makes the the contribution reductions quite a tricky exercise. In that, we obviously from the from the members' point of view, it's in their interest for the reduction to be as
Large as possible, but from the public's point of view, we must ensure that we have the reserves to meet meet claims. So it is a balancing exercise of both those interests, and that's the fund is set up to take into account both those sets of interests. Yeah, maybe I follow up. I mean, we don't want to look too arbitrary.
You know, so when we are talking about a reduction, we also need to convince the public that, well, because the reserve is enough. I mean, we also need to make sure the legal profession is not just looking at the interests of the profession, but also is considering the public interest. So any change, any
Thank you, Chairman. In terms of the drafting issues that I raised in connection with the Chinese text of the Intenti Amendment Rules, I tend to agree with the having considered the Law Society's response. I tend to agree with them that the issues wouldn't affect the meaning of the provisions.
But paragraph eight one D is a new provision added, and it describes that the company has a discretion to take over the conduct of the claim on some circumstances. So would you mind tell tell us a little bit more on on what sort of circumstances apart from on your brief you.
said that if the sole practitioner who has passed away, I would like to know if there are any other circumstances that the company would exercise that specific discretion to take over the claim directly. Very very rarely, I've been involved with the PIS for for many years now. I've never known the company.
Takeover conduct. The present provision is a little bit illogical in its operation because there's no reason why, if the company does take over conduct, why those costs do not erode the limit of indemnity. I can envisage a situation where an indemnified wishes to contest a claim.
The company doesn't. We exercise the SC clause, and the SC clause finds in the company's favour. But nevertheless, the indemnified may insist on on defending. Now it this provision now allows the company to step in and take over and and
O.K.好。
Okay, so.
Chance to get get more reduction, isn't it?
OK，好啦，好啦，OK，so，嗯。
Mr. Hoey or any any any other question? Yeah, okay.
Reduction on over30% of the premium. Yes, correct.
But anyway, yeah. Okay, so I think members.
into the rules, cover for innocent partners, which is presently excluded.
potentially looking at cover for disciplinary proceedings, you know that arise out of a practice not not law society disciplinary proceedings, but regulatory proceedings of other sorts. So, I think you know there is a general
That will be in the interest of the public in the public. Okay, and that would expedite the entire progress because if you step in, then you would avoid further dispute on that point. Well, depending, we can step in at any time. So yes, if we decided to step in in you know before trial, then yes, we could settle before trial and say on the.
And my opinion is, I think a lot of members of this panel have already raised. We pretty much look forward to the reduction of the premium because you see many of our fellow legal practitioners face a lot of burden on on the premium, and probably you would understand, yeah.
how the law society function or has been trying to achieve some sort of the reduction in the premium. I think the law society may provide some of the schemes and some of the decisions that we had taken for the last five or six years, and and that actually.
provide a a substantial reduction in terms of the premium contribution, so that that that's actually a very issue that the law society has been considering and in in fact implementing. So that may also help members to understand how we operate better. Thank you. If if I may add as well, because
The Law Society and the board is very aware of these issues. In addition to the contribution, there are other ways in which the cover provided under the professional indemnity scheme may be enhanced, and that is part of an ongoing working group where so we're looking at things like revisiting and reviewing the the limit of indemnity, perhaps putting back.
What's word a general movement towards you know maximising the value of the PS to members? Well, I I sorry have um has she has she answered your question? Fine. Well, in in fact, I'm I'm just inviting the law society to provide more information about how we implements the reduction for our members.
I mean the law society members, so that you know this information can be also provided to the members of this committee for better understanding how the law society operates in terms of getting you know ways to reduce the premium contribution. Actually, it has been happening for the last few years. There has been thirty three.
percent reduction, the cost subsidies by the PIS scheme in favour of the law firms. So that that's actually happening. That's my invitation to Fiona. I can give you that information now. Starting in two thousand and ten, the reduction has been thirty three and a third percent for.
Every year except twelve, thirteen, and then in sixteen, seventeen, it was fifty. So the reduction has been going since ten, eleven. So every single year, there was no reduction in twelve, thirteen. Okay, in twelve, thirteen, there's no reduction. But apart from that, almost every single year, there
好。
Okay.
啊，OK，好。
做板做板好啊，OK。
是係英文咧，各位委員。
Then we will go to page three.
中英文哦，好好好，好啊！
誒，我問下佢哋咯，好嘛，好嘛。
Page three， we read。
and former principal, the deletion for the purposes of schedule one two.
C誒C B四二六七足一六至一七括弧零二。
on the panel solicitor, the definition there was amendment on the definition on panel solicitor.
Okay, so let's let's start from page one. There's no amendment. So from page two, we have some interpretation on the former practice. So there was a deletion for the purposes of schedule.
咁咯，我睇翻英文啦，好嘛？哦，咁一係我哋睇翻英文啦，好嘛？嚇，so refer誒，we will refer back to the the paper number CB誒，bracket four two six seven stroke um sixteen to seventeen bracket O two，we will go through all the proposed amendment，yeah。
Not bad, isn't it? Not bad. Yeah, but I also noticed that there's a one more good thing on the amendment. Because I read from the proposed amendment on the on the situation that if there is any dispute between the indemnified and also the company on whether there should be any settlement and.
And I think previously you would appoint the law society would appoint a senior council to give opinion, but now is only appoint a council only. So that will save us a lot lot of cost, isn't it? Yeah. Depending on the council. Well, that implies probably we have more.
誒，同時咧，噉我諗我就同大家講講，而家咧，我哋可以move on去誒嗰個誒條例個條文嗰度，佢有啲修改啦。噉佢就會係誒律師會嘅代表都會同大家即係我哋一路高呼一次嘅。咁誒，我哋睇一睇我哋嗰個paper嘅number咧，我畀翻大家咧就係L C。
嚇，呢個就係嗰個誒文件嘅編號嚟嘅。咁如果大家誒唔反對嘅話，不如我就邀請大家誒高呼一次嗰個文件好嘛？噉我哋睇一睇佢哋嗰啲嘅修改。如果大家委員隨時可以提出意見，都可以誒隨時嘅。噉我想問下大家好唔好？我哋睇翻誒睇翻中文定還？
They added these.
any problem?
拍B。
Okay，no more problem。
and also we have a
The I think is.
actually，I I also mentioned that on the。
所以你 have widened your scope of indemnity, right? Okay.
provision of indemnity on next page. So the
We have a extra word added on qualified. Is that qualified or which way is that?
The related cause is the amendment is probably you add there is A and B.
That is probably including the practice on the China appointed a testing officer and also the civil civil celebrant of marriage.
on schedule three on the paragraph eight d, so I have done my question already. Okay, so we move on with the
So any problem on that? No, okay. Then we will carry on on page four. I think there's a amendment on the related cost.
the deletion the the actually the sentence on costs and expenses incur blah blah blah has been removed and it was replaced by the word related costs.
哦，OK，Yeah，So apart from the amendment to the definition of panel solicitor， there are three more sentence on JKL added to the definition of practice.
OK。
any problem?
啊！
on the area of practice.
Based on their merits, right?
所以，你你，我們 allow to do that。
In other words， I think we probably have more choice.
So if there's no problem, we move on to.
Okay， so next page， there's no amendments， I think。
有關連重費嗰度嚇，已經嗰度define咗，係啊。
所以，那 allows us to appoint a firm of solicitors which is not on the panel.
Yeah, related cause has been already divined earlier. Yeah.
Okay, so we move on on section thirteen, the disputes. Cross out the first sentence on any dispute or difference, blah blah blah. You just
呃，the next page on schedule one. Schedule one, I think they they just simply remove the bracket rules two, four and nine, replaced by R R two, four and nine and schedules two and three.
substitute by subject to paragraph 81c blah blah blah and the the quantum of any claim blah blah blah has been removed and quantum of any claim in respect of which indemnity is to be provided is replaced.
no, no, we go through to we move on to next page and there would be 17 on the panel of firms of solicitor. The original version was removed and substituted by the subparagraph one and two.
嗯。
Paragraph 14。
any other problem?
If no, we move on.
啊， we.
Move on on page.
on that particular paragraph.
on page thirteen.
and then we move on to page ten.
any other question on the interest?
There's a brand new paragraph, so.
on the principle, making good or failures, blah blah blah.
page eleven and twelve, there's no amendment on page thirteen.
insert paragraph five on interest on overdue contributions.
睇下page ten，OK，page ten，page ten，the I think paragraph D there would be amendment，呃，it was removed and substituted by the new paragraph。
Right.
schedule two。
page sixteen.
Okay, so.
page sixteen。
Okay, members happy with that.
No, then we move on to.
on the worst end compromise.
any other question on that particular paragraph? No.
But feel free to raise the question because.
Generally speaking， I think settlement include compromises， isn't it？ Yeah。
I think that that's a number fourteen. So we move on to page fifteen. Page fifteen.
Schedule Two， I think you have removed paragraph two, subsection D。
There's amendment on the wordings of fun, fun and these rules on paragraph D, and also we insert a sort of a new paragraph or the company acting in good faith, blah blah blah.
長時間討論這在委員會，關於有無區別，之間和解和妥協。我們研究了各種案例和字典定義。最終，我們決定我們無法區分，因此，為更好的草擬，我們會我們會只是。
I think you did raise that question in your in your letter. Do you or no? Okay。或者我可以問問佢點解？啊，OK好，OK。Um um, if the representative from law society, uh, would be able to explain a little bit more on the reason on deleting the word and compromise, or we we spent quite.
no。
嗯，OK。
on that too.
any other question?
是deleted。
members happy with that?
on the exclusions.
或private court and disbursement and disbursements。
In that case, we move on to page 18. Page 18.
We have deleted the paragraph.
any other question on that particular amendment on exclusions?
The company may waive in writing a whole the right to be reimbursed，something like that. So
and I think paragraph B we substitute with a new paragraph. If in relation to any claim, there's no admission or finding of acceptance or blah blah blah.
the sentence of the deductible applicable to debt payment as the company may request and interest on the amount blah blah blah and also the the we add the words on the former principle each principle and former principle, yep.
The company may pay or include that was deleted, and we add a new paragraph at any time pay or include in any payment made out of from blah blah blah, and and and then we move on to the next few sentence of the we have removed another sentence and substitute by.
Is a ten paragraph ten subsection ten which arises from circumstances or occurring when the receipts has not been issued to indemnity blah blah blah. So that was deleted, and also on subsection D direct or indirect loss by the indemnified of the amount of his fees or.
do we need it?
啊！
did we not do that one?
啊，yeah，啊，legal adviser，yeah，please。
then that would cause all kinds of problems. Got it.
Okay，then，we，move，on，to，page，nine，sorry，yeah。
just a minor, a minor one, so just simply move up to.
May I ask a question on paragraph ten? Actually, it was duly deleted.
After deletion of the，所以now the section 11 would be section 10，the 11會 become 10，yeah。
this provision is talking about on the circumstance that the company will not provide indemnity to the indemnified or a former solicitor in respect of, and then we have all those.
consequently, after deleting the subparagraph 10, do we need to renumber 11 to become or upgrade it into paragraph a new paragraph 10? It's a numbering.
as I explained before, the better course would probably to just to add an annotation after the deleted paragraph Roman 10 to say omitted or or deleted something to that effect, so as not to change the numbering, because that could have you know cross referencing implications.
嗯，thanks， chairman. I think because there could be cross referencing issues if you renumber the paragraph. So I think from a drafting perspective, it may be better just to delete it as as as omitted or deleted. I see. Otherwise, there may be other provisions which refer to Roman element X one.
But in the new version, when it is duly released on the day, and there will be the new number substitute, isn't it? You mean? Yeah. Right now, of course, I understand. Because for for for reference purpose, we have. But I think it's really a question for for for the DRJ really when they when they promulgate the new amended version. But
all those circumstances. So paragraph ten, which reads which arise from circumstances occurring when a receipt has not been issued to the indemnified under rule nine because of the failure of any principal to comply with any provision of these rules. So I think.
please correct me if I'm wrong. So in the past, obviously if there is a failure of the of the principle to comply with the rules, obviously you would not indemnify them. But right now, because you delete this clause, does it mean that if there is a failure on the principle to comply with the
是太平。
and。
Thank you.
佢就直診都review㗎。
I.C.好似噉樣咯，留翻喺度。
for the purposes，yeah，so it is substitute。
These rules， you still have discretion to indemnify them， yeah。
哦，right，okay。links in with special the redrafting a special condition nine at the end of schedule three。
And page twenty, there seems that it seems that there's no amendment. And page twenty one.
I see. And the provision of indemnity is is not so much a discretion as as it must be provided within the terms and conditions of of the rules. Okay.
Thank you. So we move on to page nineteen. Page nineteen, the deductibles for the purpose.
I think to to answer Mr. Ho's question just now, you raised the point that whether the number should be substituted on paragraph 10. I read some of the reference on the on the law. If it would read like repealed.
page twenty one there are few amendments in respect of any on section four and on section seven the non-compliance actually the number of the provision has been changed on one bracket two bracket z bracket seven is substitute.
It's an expansion. Excuse me, it's expansion of cover. So the indemnity year under the PIS runs from the one st of October to the thirty one st of September. Thirty th of September, isn't it? Thirty th of September. So and under the rules, all the indemnified firms must submit their gross fee incomes.
within that timetable, sometimes firms are late, not many, and therefore the receipt that we issued is delayed. Now, under the old rules, technically, if a claim arose in that period, then that we wouldn't provide indemnity. Ah, I see. But now we will. I see. I see. I see.
D, isn't it?
Am I correct? Yes, you are. Okay, yes.
previously there was a type of the old meeting long ago.
the the word with with hold withheld
removed it and substitute by a new paragraph.
Okay, so the last thing is to add.
所以，他們 move  The paragraphs entirely to eight, one.
Right. Okay, let's move on, and we have.
哦，Right，OK，OK。
We got another chance to have further reduction on the on the premium then.
嗯，the whole paragraph has been removed and add and what has been inserted? the
And how about the provision section number eight? Section number eight, the
So page number twenty two, page number twenty two, section C is actually.
哦，OK，OK，所以Previously the bracket two was omitted，所以 now we we need to insert that back。
item one if a difference or dispute arises between the indemnifier and the company oh that's the question I raise yeah because right now we don't need senior counsel we only need counsel so that will save our cost.
subsection item three the removal of the senior council yes that is referring to the item one we don't need the senior council anymore we only need council the council will be replaced it.
It would be like repealed on on such a subject. Yeah, so so that will we will just simply leave it blank and with the wording repealed, so that we know that we have actually removed that particular paragraph. Yeah, please. Also, the LN number reference, just so you can check which instrument the the repealing.
Any question, members?
呃，十Paragraph D。
嗯， yes， OK。
and claim an。
你，我insert paragraph C。
If no, we move on to page twenty three. Page twenty three.
The previous sentence shall procure that blah blah blah has been removed, it and.
Because bracket three has already been removed and inserted with replaced by bracket C.
subsection two, the indemnified must not divide the company, the the
subparagraph C. Any circumstances of which the indemnifier becomes aware during the period of indemnity and which may bracket blah blah blah.
That's the question I raised earlier. Yeah, on what sort of circumstances would that happen? But, but as you mentioned, that's rare circumstances. Yeah, okay.
subject to subparagraph bracket C, the company may, in its discretion and at any time, take over in the name of indemner the conduct of the defence or settlement.
Right, so and then the subsection five. If you notice, is given to the company under sub paragraph two B or bracket. Now is bracket C, is no longer bracket three.
effectively moved the paragraph C three to C，所以instead of C三變到B C啊。啊，OK，所以實際上section three is is replaced by the item C，the whole thing。
Okay, so on subsection ten, the on request the indemnifier shall give all information and assistance that the claims committee or panels panels solicitors may reasonably require to just to add the words or panels solicitors.
嗯。
on that.
啊！第二個係咩？
O.K.
Right.
Right, if
Okay, so.
Any other question?
啊！呢個係邊個嚟？即係呢個。
哦，有一個，OK，O three。
係，
Okay, so I think we have gone through the draft and it's all agreeable to us and and the.
There is another one. This should be the last one, yeah. Okay, the last one on the. What's the heading of that in the?
If there is no more question, I think we have gone through the all proposed amendments. It seems that the members agreeable are all agreeable to this to these all proposed amendments. We go back to.
I reckon it should have, it it it it ought to be changed early on. Anyway, well，中國委託公證人改翻個正確名啫。Just proper name of that China appointed attesting officer.
Right, the last page special condition. The original paragraph is removed, and we insert a brand new paragraph on special condition, which is split to subsection one and two.
solicitors practice rules to be led ahead. I think the the Chinese wording is change. 啊，中國委任的見證人員咧，而家就要改翻，就係中國委託公證人。
噉啊！打輸嘅。
The new rules.
嗯嗯嗯。
即係我哋extend咗去。
所以，我諗啲會議係今日完。There's no need to have another meeting. 好，Thank you.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, so I think probably after 18 of January, it's just a due process. Yeah.
I.T. and and in that case, I think we have done this all draft amendment. Okay, so I.
Right, so I I think members would agree that there's no need to have another meeting. Right, we have done all this. Right, I think we.
no okay no no it doesn't so in fact we could issue then the notice and the commencement date could be as soon as as soon as practicable practicable yeah okay okay again
係咪要問下嘅？即係唔好問佢哋。OK， so OK， um， would the law society representative be able to tell us when would be the proposed commencement of the rules？
Okay, well, yes, my colleague has just reminded me that according to the time schedule for our work, I think we will.
冇㗎啦，冇㗎啦。Okay， so I think members agree to the view submitted by Law Society on the particular letter they have submitted earlier on， and also the response of the legal adviser。 It seems that we don't insist on any further amendment on that Chinese wording， so we would adopt the view of the Law Society。
We haven't actually discussed the precise dates, but we have no reason to. I mean, we may as well just pick a date as soon as possible. There's no no timetable yet. Okay, okay, legal adviser, please. Thank you. Does it have to coincide with the commencement of the new?
嗯嗯。
Thank you.
Yeah, we have already extended the scrutinise period of the two amendment rules to 18th of January 2017. Okay, so on the 6th of January we will go through the House Committee first, and then on the 18th of January we'll report to the Legislative Council.
We have just done it. Yeah, we have just done it. I would agree. Yeah. Okay, right. Okay. So in that case, I have to thank all the representatives from the law society and thank you for all your good effort in drafting this amendment rules and thank you for legal adviser and all the colleagues on all your effort. Yeah.